A Guide to the Papers of Base Hospital 41 1905-2009
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- Photo taken at Elks National Home in Bedford 1978, 1 Photograph, color 3.25x3.5 (Box-folder 004-021)
- Photo taken at Elks National Home in Bedford 1978, 1 Photograph, color 3.25x3.5 (Box-folder 004-022)
  Left: Nate Adams
- Photo taken at Elks National Home in Bedford 1978, 1 Photograph, color 3.25x3.5 (Box-folder 004-023)
  2nd from right: Nate Adams, far right: Glenn B. Updike
- Photo taken at Elks National Home in Bedford 1978, 1 Photograph, color 3.25x3.5 (Box-folder 004-024)
- Caption: "Maison D'educaton de la Legion D'honneur" ca. 1918, 1 Negative strip w 4 images (Box-folder 004-025)
- Caption: "The park of the school when we arrived" ca. 1918, 1 Negative strip w 4 images (Box-folder 004-026)
  The park is the l'Ecole de la Legion D'honneur park.
- Caption: "The park later. Besseneau tents in front with about 500 patients and Marquise tents back with about 1700 beds. The later extended well over to the left but are obscured by the trees." ca. 1918, 1 Negative strip w 4 images (Box-folder 004-027)
- Caption: "Dining-room of Base Hospital 41, St. Denis, France with seating capacity of 500" ca. 1918, 1 Negative strip w 4 images (Box-folder 004-028)
- Caption: "The fracture ward" ca. 1918, 1 Negative strip w 4 images (Box-folder 004-029)
- Caption: "Colonel Cabell, Colonel Goodwin, Miss Cowling, Major Venable, Lieutenant Caylor, Major Old and Captain Sharp" ca. 1918, 1 Negative strip w 4 images (Box-folder 004-030)
- Caption: "French Marmites. A part of one of the kitchens of 41 at St. Denis" ca. 1918, 1 Negative strip w 4 images, 1 envelope (Box-folder 004-031)
- Rose taken from Lafayette's tomb was placed by [Woodrow] Wilson. 1918 December 22, 1 envelope, 1 rose (Box-folder 004-032)
- Inventory of memorabilia donated by B. P. Chamberlain on behalf of Base Hospital 41 1979 June, 1 TD (Box-folder 004-033)
- The Clayton Brothers World War I by William H. Clayton 2009 July, 1 copy of book, 1 ALS (Box-folder 004-034)
  William Clayton writes about his uncles, William Harold Clayton, Fredrick Van Clayton and Silas Walter Clayton. Silas was assigned to Base Hospital 41. He also includes copies of pictures and letters. William donated the book.